One day you'll be back
When you're done dreaming
At last
Now this road has passed
And you're done wandering...
Evelyn!
Will you come back?
Oh, how people change
But you... were never like
The others
Babe
Now that's the same
But, oh how people change
You were never like
The others, babe
Now that's the same
One day you'll be back
You keep dreaming
But you will come home
You're late.
Did I say you could sit?
You can start by cleaning the study.
And don't take all day this time.
While you're there,
you can take the bin out.
Hello, Lorna.
Where are you going?
I thought I'd finished for the day.
You finish when I say.
- But there is nothing left to do.
- Oh, there's plenty left to do.
You can start by rubbing my feet.
May I go to the toilet?
No.
But I...
I think it's better
that you stay by my feet
and continue doing
what I asked you to do.
Come in.
I finished sweeping the porch.
- Can I go now?
- Did you wash my things?
- What things?
- You keep forgetting.
I left a whole pile for you.
Okay, but can you show me
how to use the machine?
You won't be using the machine.
- It's all done.
- You rinsed the soap off?
Let's see if you've done
your job properly.
What's this doing here?
This was on the pile.
This was on the pile for you to wash.
Sorry, I..
- I didn't see it.
- How could you not see it?
I.. I can wash it now,
it's not a problem.
No, you can't wash it now
and it is a problem,
because I have other plans for you now.
It's just a few minutes,
that's all it takes.
I've waited enough already.
You haven't washed anything properly
and you forgot this.
- Sorry.
- You will be.
- What are you going to do?
- A little punishment.
- But I... I can do it now.
- It's too late.
Lie down.
Open your mouth.
Thank you, so much.
Not too cold?
The colder the better.
By highlighting
the geographical proximity
of Gryllotalpa gryllotalpa
and Gryllotalpa vineae,
these recordings should demonstrate
how fundamental sound is
as a classifying factor.
Species identification will partly
rely upon the duration of one syllable
usually in milliseconds.
The carrier wave expressed in kilohertz
is another factor in identification.
Since these species are so visually
indistinguishable from each other,
the sound they produce
should differentiate the two.
Dr Schuller, if we could hear
the Gryllotalpa gryllotalpa please.
And now if we hear
Gryllotalpa vineae, please?
Did I say you could stop?
'Cynthia.
'This is all I ever dreamed about,
'to be owned by you.
'To be used by you.
'I can't tell you how happy I am.
'I never thought I could find
someone like you.
'I never thought it would be possible.
'I won't let you down, Cynthia.
'Never.
'I won't let you down.
'As long as I'm yours,
'I remain alive.
'I love you, Cynthia.
'I love you.'
You're late.
Did I say you could sit?
You can start by cleaning the study.
And don't take all day this time.
So you've finished already?
Good for you. I have something else
for you to do now.
Come here.
What are you doing?
I told you to clean my boots.
Do that again and you'll be punished.
You don't listen, do you?
You just don't listen!
Now you'll see what happens
when you don't listen.
When you're being bad and lazy.
...what distinguishes
Thaumetopoea pityocampa
from other Tussock moths
is the communal nature of their larvae.
The sun gives them enough energy
for their nocturnal foraging.
You like it?
- That's really nice.
- Yes?
Yes.
Tell me something.
There's so many things to tell you.
Far too many things.
But I can start with
how much I love you...
and how happy I am
that you're here with me.
- How happy I am...
- Talk about the other things.
I'm not happy.
I'm not happy with you at all.
- Really?
- Really.
What have I done?
It's what you haven't done.
You haven't been a good maid.
And I have to do
everything I want with you.
You're mine now.
Keep talking.
Say something else.
You haven't washed my panties recently.
Nor have you polished my boots.
If you want to be a good maid,
you have to do these things a lot more.
Otherwise, you'll be punished.
Keep talking.
I don't know what to say.
Just go back to the beginning, then.
I'm not happy.
I'm not happy with you at all.
Improvise!
When you work for me, it's for life.
You have to do...
whatever I want, whenever I want.
Because if you don't,
I just... might tie you up
and use you as my chair
for the afternoon.
I can read about cave crickets...
whilst you're helpless underneath me
and I put my weight
upon your face and...
you just have to lie there and wait
until I'm finished reading
my book and...
Try to have more conviction
in your voice next time.
More conviction.
Okay.
...although what distinguishes the skippers
from hair streaks, coppers and blues
is the way the clubs and antennae
gradually thicken,
often ending in hooked points.
Also, their larvae...
This is elementary level.
...pupating in silk shelters
at the base of legumes or herbs.
However, in order to survive,
the larvae need plentiful light,
which often occurs inadvertently
when livestock are grazing.
The most explicit example for this
is the larvae
of the Silver-spotted Skipper,
which feed on sheep's fescue grass,
which in turn is never allowed
to grow too plentifully by grazing cows.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dr Viridana.
Would anyone like to ask a question?
I often have trouble differentiating
between the Small and Large Skipper.
Is there any way to tell them apart?
Easy. One is large, one is small.
A lot of people have that trouble, since
they are both the same size and colour.
But the Small Skipper often holds its
wings at a 45-degree angle when resting.
Its orange colouring
is more uniform, too,
while the Large Skipper has mottled
orange patterns on its underside.
Any other questions?
Could you talk about the venation
of the Grizzled Skipper?
How do you mean?
In terms of longitudinal and cross veins
and how... how they vary in relation
to other species within the family.
Well, the Grizzled Skipper is
so visually distinctive amongst the family
that there's no need to go
into such detail on the wings.
It's the only skipper in the region
to have black markings
- and is by far the easiest to identify.
- I know.
I was just wondering how one goes
about classifying other Pyrgus species
in other regions.
I'm afraid it's something I can't answer.
This talk only concerns this region.
Any other questions? No?
Okay, well, once again,
thank you very much, Dr Viridana.
For the next talk, we'll have...
- What's that look?
- Nothing.
...parasitic Hymenoptera.
I feel so stupid, Cynthia.
- Stupid about what?
- That Grizzled Skipper nonsense.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
- You don't think I'm stupid, do you?
Of course not. It's okay.
What?
Can you let me go now?
No.
So, you would like your lover
to sleep on top of you?
Yes.
I make two types of bed
for what you want.
One where the compartment underneath
slides out and then back in,
or one where the bed mattress lifts up
and then can be pulled down
and locked once you're inside.
Once you're inside, it's the same.
It's just the sensation of being put in
and set free that is different.
Which one would you recommend?
The bed lifting up is often more favoured
than the drawer-style compartment.
Sometimes the drawers can get stuck.
Thankfully, that usually happens
when they're out, rather than in,
but it's a critical moment when they're
about to be locked up for the night
and then realise that they can't be.
Well, the bed lifting up
seems fine by me.
It's just a simple spring
that lifts the bed up.
Customers find the slamming effect of the
bed closing down on them very dramatic.
That bed is very popular.
I think I made one for someone
in the neighbourhood a few months ago.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Who was that?
- I can't remember her name.
Let me think...
It's the house with the wisteria porch
and yellow colonnade,
a few minutes down the lane.
- Yellow colonnade?
- That's got to be Ambrosia.
Is that her house?
She might have painted
the colonnade another colour,
but that's got to be Ambrosia.
I'm surprised you could make a bed
big enough for her to be locked in.
Okay, then it's the same customer
I'm thinking of.
But yes, that design
is a lot more popular
and because of the spring,
it's easy to lift up.
With both designs,
there's a lock at each end of the bed,
but even without those,
the weight of one's lover
sleeping on top
means that it's almost
impossible to escape.
- And...
- I can also add metal hooks to the inside
if you like having your hands and feet
tied to something.
That sounds perfect.
And how long does it take
once we've placed an order?
Oh, usually around eight weeks.
Eight weeks!
I'm afraid there's a lot of demand
and it takes time to make each bed.
Eight weeks?
Is there any way
you can offer a faster service?
It's just that Evelyn's birthday
is coming up
and I was planning this as a present.
- Oh, it depends when your birthday is.
- Two weeks.
It will be my birthday in two weeks.
Two weeks?
It's impossible. I'm sorry.
We can offer you extra, if it helps.
We have a mount
of extremely rare Satyrids.
You wouldn't find those
even in the museums.
They're worth far more
than Nymphalids or Burnets.
Evelyn's right.
It's a highly collectable mount.
I'm sorry, but I have too much pressure
from other customers.
And I cannot do it any sooner
than eight weeks. I'm so sorry.
Well, we'd have to discuss it,
anyway, before we order.
It's okay.
There will be another birthday.
If you like, we could look for something
that is not so much in demand.
The bed would have been perfect.
Would a human toilet
be a suitable compromise?
Really?
- Well...
- I really have to go now.
But wait.
Don't you want to hear about this?
Oh, I have to go.
I told you I had to leave.
I'm sorry for being so abrupt.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
It was a pleasure for me.
I'll be back in an hour,
will I meet you here?
I'll be here.
Don't make any orders
without consulting with me.
I won't, don't worry. I'll let you know.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
So... there are two types available.
The basic model allows you
to experience...
What is that look?
There.
Just a little longer, please.
I'm in such agony.
Rubbing it's not going to help.
You need an ice pack
and some painkillers.
Do you want me to call a doctor?
No, it's okay.
My back does this every few years.
It'll get better.
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks.
- Tell me?
- Okay.
You don't sound enthusiastic.
It says to be cold.
Yes, but not now.
And one thing I forgot to write -
don't talk about it.
- Just surprise me.
- I know, I know.
Well, you were a bit slow
to surprise me last time.
Well, it's not a surprise
if you're expecting it, is it?
I know, but... what I mean by surprise
is within 24 hours.
But not in the first hour,
because that wouldn't be a surprise.
Okay, okay.
And not in the last hour, either.
I'm just all frustrated by then.
So within 22 hours, then?
Yes.
Anything else?
No.
Come in.
It's all done.
You rinsed the soap off?
Let's see if you've done
your job properly.
What's this doing here?
How long do I have to stay in here for?
For as long as I want.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
Can you breathe in there?
Yes!
Pinastri.
Pinastri!
- What happened?
- Nothing.
- Just a mosquito bite.
- Aw.
I told you,
it's more fun to sleep with me.
Maybe you can put me back in there,
but just don't tie me.
Come to bed.
'This is all I ever dreamed about.
'This is all I ever dreamed about.'
Pinastri.
Lie down.
Open your mouth.
Try turning the tap on.
- Why did you write about mole crickets?
- Why not?
Such ugly things.
No wonder they hide under the ground.
Ugly maybe, but beautifully eloquent.
Aargh!
Are you okay?
Okay. Just about.
It would just be nice
if you volunteered to rub my back.
Sorry.
I didn't know you needed anything.
Well, you can see that I'm in pain.
Well, it's not exactly inspiring
to see you dressed like that.
Good thing you're not a doctor, then.
That's really some look you have there!
Even the tramps are less shabby.
I'm starting to wonder why I bothered
buying you a whole wardrobe.
I need an instruction manual to get
into half of the things you buy me.
I would just like to feel comfortable,
thank you very much.
This is giving me a headache.
You're not going to turn it off?
Did you ask me to?
How long do I have to stay in here for?
For as long as I want.
Morning, Lorna.
Do you want to go with me
to the library?
What time is it?
It's around two.
I thought we could also
have an ice cream after.
Another time.
The Institute will close for winter
any day soon.
I know.
So you're not coming, then?
I need to sleep if you're going
to put me in the trunk tonight.
That's news to me.
It would be nice if you did it
without having to be asked.
There used to be a time when my body
would just repair itself overnight.
It's all downhill from now.
Don't be such a pessimist!
You have many, many years left in you.
Oh, that reminds me.
On the subject of getting old.
- I spoke to Lorna the other day.
- I don't know why you bother.
What's that miserable sow
have to say, anyway?
She wanted to alert us
to some root problems with the birch.
She claims they might be
unsettling her foundations.
Let her claim away. What a nonsense.
That tree rests too far from the house
to have any effect.
Ignore her.
She's nothing
but a bloated bag of trapped wind.
She also claims she spotted you polishing
Dr Schuller's boots in her backyard.
Tell me that's just another sly rumour.
Don't be ridiculous.
You know what Lorna's like.
Are you really going to get taken in
by such idle gossip?
No, but this was rather precise.
It would hurt me more
if you denied such an accusation.
So, I'm condemned
for denying a false accusation?
- That's a good move!
- Just tell me the truth.
I'm telling you the truth.
That Lorna makes it her business
to spread dirty lies.
You polished her boots, didn't you?
Tell me.
Don't lie to me, Evelyn.
Tell me what you did.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
So what else did you two get up to?
- Nothing.
- Really?
Nothing. I swear! Nothing!
I just polished her boots.
I find that hard to believe.
Did she punish you?
- Did she punish you?
- No!
So you just polished her boots
out of pure good will?
Okay, she...
She told me off a bit.
That's all. Nothing more.
How did she tell you off?
- Let's not...
- How did she tell you off?
I don't know. Just some harsh words.
Some threats.
That's all. Then I went home.
- I bet you did.
- I didn't do anything.
We didn't kiss, we didn't touch.
Nothing, I swear.
Believe me, I didn't do anything.
That's your idea of not doing anything?
For what it's worth,
you might as well have gone all the way.
The damage has been done.
- What damage?
- You betrayed me!
Do you call that betrayal?
Why would you lie about something
if you didn't regard it as betrayal?
Because you'd automatically think
something else happened when it didn't.
- Where are you going?
- Somewhere.
Anywhere.
- Anywhere away from you.
- Please, Cynthia.
Please. I'm sorry.
That was just a bad day.
I was feeling weak. I was frustrated.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't getting what I needed here.
So, had I ordered a human toilet,
none of this would've happened then?
I'm sorry. I'm weak and I'm sorry.
Cynthia! Please!
Please, Cynthia!
I love you. Please.
The tunnelling larvae of Xestobium
rufovillosum are a severe pest
in both buildings
and in the timber trade.
Their trail of devastation
isn't as patterned
as species from the Scolytidae family.
Their galleries and tunnels
deep within the wood
are distinctive to each species.
Xestobium rufovillosum favours oak,
whether living or felled.
'Although seldom seen,
its presence is often felt
'by the sinister tapping sound it makes
'to attract a mate during the spring.'
Wait! Wait!
Now, my love.
A small birthday treat for you.
All I can say is
I hope you like it as much as I do.
Is this a joke?
No, no.
The ingredients for your birthday cake.
Which you are going to make.
Here's the recipe.
And while you're doing that,
I'll go change into something nicer.
- I don't know if I can...
- Oh, you have to.
Read the recipe
and make the cake.
I want you ready by nine.
Now, put it here.
Where's my fork?
- What about...?
- Don't come so close.
Your breath is like a hyena.
Now, lie down.
Here.
- This is not funny.
- Did I say you could speak?
Pinastri.
Pinastri, Pinastri.
Oh, if we could all just say Pinastri
to end our torments.
Two by two
Watching them over
Follow as they're told
Moving through
Watch them grow older
Follow when they go
Ah...
Two by two
Love with no answer
Hiding the untold
Moving through
Loving the other
Hide the overgrown
Ah
'What's this doing here?
'This was on the pile.
'This was on the pile for you to wash.'
'I'm sorry. I didn't see it.'
'How could you not see it?
I left it there on the pile.
'Answer me. How could you not see it?'
'But I can wash it now.
It's not a problem.'
'No, you can't wash it now
and it is a problem,
'because I have other plans
for you now.'
- 'Sorry.'
- 'You will be.'
Pinastri.
'Pinastri.'
Cynthia.
Can you sit on me?
Please?
'The anatomy of Gryllotalpidae
'is highly modified
for a subterranean existence.
'The squat and broad velvety haired body
'with flattened claws and short antennae
'is designed to burrow into the soil,
'occasionally to depths of one metre.'
The spade-like forelimbs
are enlarged and very powerful,
ideally suited for digging.
'With the advent of winter,
'all Gryllotalpidae retreat
into their burrows.'
There they will remain in hibernation,
still and dormant,
until the spring sun
warms the soil enough
to stir them from their slumber.
It's all done.
You rinsed the soap off?
Let's see if you've done
your job properly.
What's th...?
What's this doing here?
I left it on the pile.
I left it on the pile for you to wash.
Sorry... I...
I didn't see it.
How could you not see it?
I left it there
on the pile.
But I can wash it now.
It's not a problem.
No, you can't wash it now.
And it is a problem.
I can do this. Okay...
I'm sorry.
Please don't be mad at me.
It's okay.
I can change, if this is what
it does to you. I can change.
All this is just a luxury.
The important thing is you.
No, but maybe you'll end up
resenting me. We can't win.
How can I resent you?
I love you.
I know have a different way
of showing it.
But I love you.
You don't believe me, do you?
What do you want me to do to prove it?
Just tell me.
Just tell me what to do and I'll do it.
Oh, please, believe that I love you.
- 'Are you okay?'
- 'Of course.'
- 'Are you sure?'
- 'I'm sure.
'I'm sure, don't worry.
'Everything's fine.
'Everything's more than fine.'
- 'Really?'
- 'Really.
'Everything is fine.'
The growing sun, the end of spring
The first part beginning
The coat of arms is fading
Your golden chain is breaking
Soldier at dawn
Holy one
Come away
Go at dawn
The growing sun
Shadows bring
The last to part is waiting
Your coat of arms is fading
Your golden chain is breaking
Soldier at dawn
Holy one
Come away